time comes for car insurance,
you get confused about getting insurance
online, you want very good
offers online, there are very good pricing
and offline is a bit expensive,
but we feel that one advantage is that
we can get it directly from the showroom, if there is any
problem then we can tell the dealer, so
this confusion persists and we are
not able to understand which insurance to take
and in that case many times we
take the wrong insurance, when the last receiver was done,
I did it online, now when I got it done
offline, I have tasted
both online and offline, I have come to know
what are the positives and negatives of both, and that is what I will
share with you today, along with that I will
also tell you which one you should take,
and there are some disadvantages in it compared to the other,
but in the end I will tell you one such thing
due to which they will be almost equal, in fact
you will definitely benefit, so
in the last couple of the video, my name
is Mitra, you watch Coat Life and please
subscribe to the channel, so let's make a point,
this is the first time you will
get that cheap line online.  You will get it
expensive and this is the only thing towards online
that also stops the positive. After this,
whatever positive I will tell you, they will all be from showrooms and
not from online. Secondly, in most
of the cases, if you live in a second year or third
year city, then in most of the
cases, where you get your car repaired,
where you get the car serviced,
which comes to the room, from which the money for your
car is taken, it will not be cashless on that panel, the
panel which you are taking online will
not be cashless, okay, you will have to pay the gas first,
whatever, suppose your car met with an
accident, you spent Rs. 200,000,
then you will have to pay from your pocket,
you will get the bill from the service center,
you will submit the bill to the company and
then we will talk about the amount you will get,
okay, secondly, there may be a
thanks less garage in your city, but
then it looks after all the vehicles, it is the same
for Tata, it is the same for Maruti, it is the same
for Ford, it is the same for them too,
so there it is not an expert for
any particular company's vehicle, so
how is it  We cannot even do that if we
buy it online, so one disadvantage we face is
that we
cannot buy it cashless from a particular showroom where it is available for free. The
second thing I noticed was
that a friend of mine had an accident with his car, so since
last year I was
looking at accidental cases a lot because
I also knew that the insurance of my car had to be renewed. When we
meet people from offline, they behave like this. So
when we go online and those who are
not on the panel of that company, be it
Maruti, Tata or anyone else, the
behavior of their staff is such that
if you have bought it through the company or
through the showroom, then it will be better with you. I
mean, if you have bought it from outside, then
you are not treated so well. There was
a tweeter there,
he was fighting over this thing that you are taking in those who have got
your insurance done quickly, there is a
delay in 10 days for them,
you are making me run around for three days, sometimes bring this document,
many wards, comments, then it takes me one and a half
months.  If you are giving time for cashless and if it is not delayed then it
means there were a lot of disputes with them.
This organization had taken contract number 18 and
talked to them. You told me that you had to
press in great difficulty and did not
even get the amount you were supposed to take in insurance claim. I will
tell my mother why you did not get it. So the second thing is about
behavior. Then the third thing is if you have
started this program through a company then you will get your car repaired
quickly and take it home. If you have got it done from outside,
I am talking about most of the cases, I am not talking about 10%.
In some cases you get it done online or offline, it does not make
any difference. But
generally if I talk about 90% of the cases, this is what happens. If you have done
this program online then
you will get your car repaired quickly and you have got it done from
someone else and
not from that company, then it may take
time. Then you are
dependent on their mercy as to how much time the service center is
giving you. And let me tell you one more thing,
we assume that by holding an insurance company,
National
Insurance. Okay,
if you take insurance of such insurance  If you
take it through Maruti or through someone's panel against Tata, then you will
get cashless, if you take National Insurance from
outside, that is, suppose
you take the policy from the market, then you will
not get cashless there, this system has been given,
they have their own channels, so
if you take it through that channel, then
you get cashless from any insurance company,
otherwise you will not get cashless, you will check the playlist, there are
many things like that,
nowadays companies are working in this type, there
are car companies in car showrooms so that you can get 19 A
lens for yourself, then one more thing which
you will not get online, the online people will never recommend you to
subscribe to this channel, yes, I am
telling you not to do it online or the offline
showroom people may
subscribe themselves after watching the video and if they tell you, then
please subscribe to the channel, there were
problems online, now
see, I am going by adding all the things which the sweet people give,
now they feel like
abusing someone, breaking someone's head,
but what were they able to do to separate anyone, they were
just  I was able to call Policy Bazaar, I was with
Policy Bazaar, if they were not with me, then if I have to do it
outstation, then you will have to do it, so they are providing the
facility, they will give you a
closure but it can happen there and
with someone else, there will be a lot of problems,
you will have to do a lot of work yourself, you
may have to submit it in the files, then you will have to
spend money from your pocket, so
this problem also exists in online and when
his claim was passed, he
told me that he had earned Rs. 8000,
why did he talk to the company
online, you told me that they
charge a service charge, there are some changes in your setup part, there are
service charges,
you can assume that they charge one of our settings,
they
told me that I got the insurance done online, this is the amount I paid, so I got the
insurance done online here, I faced a lot of
trouble,
they did not talk to me for a long time and
after so many troubles, all the problems that I had got
here,
if I had to take it for the second time, then
after seeing me in trouble, I put the car aside and said that I will do
offline insurance now  If we had talked
offline then I would have done it, it would have been expensive, so
how did I get it cheaper, I
told you, I got an online insurance of ₹1000 when they gave me a quotation, I
took insurance of ₹14000 from here for ₹
15000 offline, that was the value, no
ID was reduced, whatever I had to add, I got it done only that
and
after that I got that interest for ₹15000,
you don't have to do a little hassle, there is a
little less brotherhood with them,
that is fine, you don't need to be too rude,
you will do it comfortably, I do
n't mean if you get it at this rate, yes
if there is a difference of seven to eight thousand rupees, then
gradually it can be said to be two-three to ₹4000
and this much difference can be made on you
because we got the insurance done to
avoid trouble, this much to be troubled
and if you get it done in advance, you must have got the
engine protector done, you got the
investment cover done, if anyone comes and goes giving you a donut like that then
you  The
chances of getting a little more discount in flying also
increases if you have got three or four deals done then it is
possible that
you may get around the same price online and offline, then
you can ask
them for a discount, it is not that they have written it down, the same thing happens that
I am showing you both the things,
first they made it Rs 21000 for me,
then it became around Rs 15000, main
friends, so that's all for today, if
you want to avoid trouble, in 90% of the cases
please do it through showroom and in 1% of the cases it can be done
easily online also, it is
not a big problem and
if you are in a third tier city then
I would prefer you to
take it through showroom only and have a little conversation,
you will get the discount here, so
for more videos of this type, please subscribe to the channel, if you
like this video then
like it or see you
in the next video, thank you